<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ux on Kel</title>
    <link>https://kel-staging.netlify.com/tags/ux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ux on Kel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kel-staging.netlify.com/tags/ux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BusIt</title>
      <link>https://kel-staging.netlify.com/post/busit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kel-staging.netlify.com/post/busit/</guid>
      <description>Through meeting and planning out the stages in the project we found out that BusIt had an idea of their user groups but not what each one would need, and want, to make their transit experience the best. We decided early on that the best way to engage with users was for me to get on the bus and talk to them. Through doing this we learn’t about all the small things that different people experience when taking a bus such as blind/visually impaired people using the sound of the bus to wave it down, the visually impaired using colour to find their bus on a time table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hamilton Zoo</title>
      <link>https://kel-staging.netlify.com/post/hamiltonzoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kel-staging.netlify.com/post/hamiltonzoo/</guid>
      <description>We took a user centered approach to the redesign of the website, and my role in project was to conduct user interviews, create personas, produce wireframes, and complete user testing. We found that there were a few key things that users needed to know when planning a trip to the zoo. Those being; zoo events, opening hours, ticket prices, location, and the weather conditions. We used a home page banner to show off what’s on at the zoo, followed by a bar that quickly points people to finding opening hours, ticket prices, location, and the weather conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Health Foundation</title>
      <link>https://kel-staging.netlify.com/post/mental-health-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kel-staging.netlify.com/post/mental-health-foundation/</guid>
      <description>I was tasked with interviewing users, creating personas and scenarios. I then provided my findings in an expert report to the Mental Health Foundation. Throughout this process I discovered that users were different than expected. There was a problem with the overall Information Architecture of the website. The users didn&amp;rsquo;t understand the sitemap and the terminology used on the site.
The report included a list of recommendations that could be done right away without any extra work, and a list for future projects and improvements to better help them communicate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reach</title>
      <link>https://kel-staging.netlify.com/post/reach-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kel-staging.netlify.com/post/reach-project/</guid>
      <description>My role in this project was to:
 Develop user interview questions Assist the Client in conducting interviews Create personas and scenarios Create website wireframes Develop the visual style direction Design posters.  Through user research we discovered that the users needed a website that made it easy for them to find information and get the assistance they need. This was done with a simple site structure with well defined sections and calls to action.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>